Guide to the David L. Call papers, 1977-1995.
Call, David L. papers, 1977-1995
- Faculty, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Faculty Honors, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Faculty Meetings, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Faculty Meetings, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Farm Bureau Annual Meeting, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Farm Bureau--Young Farmers & Ranchers, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Farm Credit Banks of Springfield, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Farming Systems, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Fertilizer Tax, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Finance & Business Office, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Finance & Business Office, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Finance & Business Office, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Finance & Business Office, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Floriculture & Ornamental Horticulture, Dept. of, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Floriculture & Ornamental Horticulture, Dept. of, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Food & Agricultural Sciences, Joint Council on, 1979-1982 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Food & Agricultural Sciences, Joint Council on, 1979-1982 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Food & Agricultural Sciences, Joint Council on, 1979-1982 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Food & Agricultural Sciences, Joint Council on, 1979-1982 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Food Editors, Quaker Oats, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Food Policy White Paper, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Food Processing Development Lab, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Food Safety Council, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Food Safety Council, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Food Science, Dept. of / Institute of Food Science, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Food Science, Dept. of / Institute of Food Science, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Food Science, Dept. of / Institute of Food Science, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Food Update--Scottsdale, Arizona, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Fume Hoods, 1979-1983 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- G (General Correspondence), 1981 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- GAAP (General Accounting Principles) Bill, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Gasohol, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- General Foods, 1979-1981 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- General Foods, 1979-1981 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- General Services, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Governor (NYS--Office of/ Executive Chamber), 1979-1984 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Graduate School, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Graduate School, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Grape & Wine Industry, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Grape & Wine Research, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- H (General Correspondence), 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Herbster, William G. (Senior Vice President), 1978-1984 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Herbster, William G., (Senior Vice President), 1978-1984 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Historical Documentation Project, 1981-1985 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Historical Documentation Project, 1981-1985 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Ho-Nun-De-Kah (CALS honorary society), 1980 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Human Ecology, College of, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Industrial Relations--ARCO (Atlantic Richfield Corporation), 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Industrial Relations, 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Instruction, Office of, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Instruction, Office of, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Instruction, Office of, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Integrated Pest Management (IPM), 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Integrated Pest Management (IPM), 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Integrated Pest Management (IPM), 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- International Agriculture Program, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- International Agriculture Program, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- International Agriculture Program & International Agricultural Development Service (IADS), 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- International Agriculture Program & (IADS), 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- IAD Steering Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- International Rice Research Institute, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- International Studies, Center for, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- J (General Corresondence), 1981-1984 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Job Placement, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- K (General Correspondence), 1981 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Kellogg Foundation, 1980-1983 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Kellogg Foundation, 1980-1983 (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Kellogg Foundation, 1980-1983 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Kennedy, W. Keith, Provost, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Kennedy, W. Keith, Provost, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 46)
- Kennedy, W. Keith, Provost, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 47)
- Landscape Architecture, 1978-1982 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Landscape Architecture, 1978-1982 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Langmuir Laboratory, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Latin American Studies Program, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Legislative, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Liberty Hyde Bailey Professorship, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Liberty Hyde Bailey Professorship, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Life Safety, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Long Island Horticultural Research Lab, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Long Island Horticultural Research Lab, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Long Island Research Lab, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- M (General Correspondence), 1978-1982 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Mann Library, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Matyas, Robert M. (Vice President of Planning), 1978-1981 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Media Services, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Migrants, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Milk Industry Foundation, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Milk Industry Foundation, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Milk Marketing, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Miner Institute for Agricultural Research, Inc., 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Minority Affairs, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Minority Affairs, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Minority Council, 1978-1980 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Minority Education Council, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Minority Education Council, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- N (General Correspondence), 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- NACAA (National Association County Agricultural Agents) Meeting--Ithaca, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- National Agricultural Research & Extension Users Advisory Board, 1978-1981 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- NASULGC (National Association of State Universities & Land Grant Colleges), 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- NASULGC (National Association of State Universities & Land Grant Colleges), 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- NASULGC (National Association of State Universities & Land Grant Colleges), 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Natural Resources, Dept. of, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Natural Resources, Dept. of, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- New York/Pennsylvania Dairymen's Seminar, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Nobel Foundation, Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- North Central Computer Institute, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- North Country Ag. Development Program, 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- North Country Ag. Development Program, 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Northeastern Ad Hoc Regional Council, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Nutrition Foundation, 1978-1981 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Nutrition Foundation, 1978-1981 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Nutrition Foundation, 1978-1981 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Nutrition Foundation, 1978-1981 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Nutrition Foundation, 1978-1981 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Nutrition Foundation--12/5/80, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Nutritional Sciences, Division of, 1978-1981 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Nutritional Sciences, Division of, 1978-1981 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- NY Farm Bureau, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- NY Farmers, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- NY Farmers, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- NYS Agricultural Society (photo enclosed--Gov. Hugh Carey), 1981 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- NYS Agriculture & Markets, Dept. of, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- NYS Council of Farmer Cooperatives, Inc., 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- NYS Dairy Foods, Inc., 1980 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- NYS Environmental Conservation, Dept. of, 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- NYS Fair, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- NYS Grange, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- NYS Rural Safety Council, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- NYS School Boards, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- NYS Soil & Water Conservation Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- NYS Soil & Water Conservation Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- P (General Correspondence), 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Pepsico Project--Egypt, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Personnel, 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Pesticides, 1978-1984 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Physical Space Operations, 1978-1981 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Physical Space Operations, 1978-1981 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Plant Biology, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Plant Breeding, Dept. of, 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Plant Pathology, Dept. of, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Plant Science Growth Facilities, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Policy Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Pomology, Dept. of, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Poultry & Avian Sciences, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Public Policy Coordinator (Stephan P. Johnson), 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Public Policy Coordinator, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Public Policy Coordinator, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Q (General Correspondence), 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Ramin, Richard M. (Vice President, Public Affairs), 1978-1980 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Real Estate, 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Real Estate, 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Research--General, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Research--General, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Research--General, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Research--General, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Resources Conservation Act, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Retirement, 1973-1983 (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Rhodes, Frank, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 43)
- Robison Athletic Committee, 1978-1981 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Rural Schools Program, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Rural Sociology, Dept. of, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 46)
- S (General Correspondence), 1981 (Box 10, Folder 47)
- Salaries, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 48)
- Scannell, Jim (Dean of Admissions), 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 49)
- Schuyler County Speech, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Sea Grant Institute, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 51)
- Sea Grant Institute, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 52)
- Sea Grant Institute, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Sea Grant Institute, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Senators (NYS), 1980-1983 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Sludge, 1978-1981 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Sludge, 1978-1981 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Sludge, 1978-1981 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Sludge, 1978-1981 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Spencer, James W. (Vice Provost), 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Spencer, James W., 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Sponsored Programs, Office of (Thomas Rogers), 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- State Assembly, 1980-1984 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- SUNY--General, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- SUNY--General, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- SUNY--General, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- SUNY--Academic Programs, Policy and Planning--Vice Chancellor, 1979-1981 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- SUNY--Academic Programs, Policy and Planning--Vice Chancellor, 1979-1981 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- SUNY--Academic Programs, Policy and Planning--Vice Chancellor, 1979-1981 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- SUNY--Advisory Council, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- SUNY--Advisory Council, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- SUNY--Advisory Council, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- SUNY--Advisory Council, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- SUNY--Advisory Council, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- SUNY--Advisory Council, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- SUNY--Affirmative Action, 1977-1981 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- SUNY--Agricultural & Technical College, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- SUNY--Board of Trustees, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- SUNY--Board of Trustees, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- SUNY--Campus Liaison, Deputy to the Chancellor for (Murray H. Block), 1980 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- SUNY--Capital Facilities, Vice Chancellor for, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- SUNY--Chancellor (Clifton Wharton), 1981 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- SUNY--Council of Presidents, 1979-1981 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- SUNY--Council of Presidents, 1979-1981 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- SUNY--Council of Presidents, 1979-1981 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- SUNY--Council of Presidents, 1979-1981 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- SUNY--Council of Presidents, 1979-1981 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- SUNY--Council of Presidents, 1979-1981 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- SUNY--Council of Presidents, 1979-1981 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- SUNY--Educational Services, Vice Chancellor for (James Smoot), 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- SUNY--Educational Services, Vice Chancellor for (James Smoot), 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- SUNY--Faculty & Staff Relations, Vice Chancellor for, 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- SUNY--Finance & Business, Vice Chancellor for (Harry Spindler), 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- SUNY--Finance & Business, Vice Chancellor for (Harry Spindler), 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- SUNY--Finance & Business, Vice Chancellor for (Harry Spindler), 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- SUNY--Five Year Plan, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- SUNY--Geneva, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- SUNY--Geneva, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- SUNY--Health Sciences, Vice Chancellor for (Alden Haffner), 1981 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- SUNY--Institutional Research & Analytical Studies, Office of, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- SUNY--Institutional Research & Analytical Studies, Office of, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- SUNY--Institutional Research & Analytical Studies, Office of, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- SUNY--Special Programs, Associate Chancellor for (George Blair), 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- SUNY--Special Programs, Associate Chancellor for (George Blair), 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- SUNY--University Affairs & Development, Vice Chancellor for (Robert Perrin), 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- T (General Correspondence), 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Tenure Appeals Panel, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Toxicology, 1979-1982 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Toxicology, 1979-1982 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Toxicology, 1979-1982 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Toxicology, 1979-1982 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Toxicology, 1979-1982 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Tropical Studies Inc., Organization for, 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Tropical Studies Inc., Organization for, 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Tug Hill, Temporary State Commission on, 1979-1984 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Uihlein Farm (Donor), 1981 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Unit Plan, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- United Way, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- University Council, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- University Development, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- University Unions, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- USDA (US Dept. of Agriculture), 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- USDA (US Dept. of Agriculture), 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Vegetable Crops, Dept. of, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Veterinary College, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- W (General Correspondence), 1980-1984 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Word Processing--Ad Hoc Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Word Processing--Ad Hoc Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- Word Processing--Ad Hoc Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Academic Computing Committee, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Adirondack Park Research, 1982-1984 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- Administrative Services, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- Administrative Services, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 44)
- Administrative Services, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 45)
- Administrative Services, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 46)
- Admissions, 1981-1983 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Admissions, 1981-1983 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Admissions, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Advisory Council on Agriculture--April 15-16, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Advisory Council on Agriculture--Nov. 4-5, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Advisory Council on Agriculture--Nov. 4-5, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Advisory Council on Agriculture--General, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Advisory Council on Agriculture--General, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Advisory Council Members, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Advisory Council on Agriculture--General, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Advisory Council on Agriculture--General, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Advisory Council on Agriculture--General, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Africa, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- AgPAC, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Agricultural Economics, Dept. of, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Agricultural Economics, Dept. of, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Agricultural Economics Lecture--11/17/82, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Agricultural Engineering, Dept. of, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Agricultural Engineering, Dept. of, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Agricultural Organizations, Council of, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Agricultural Organizations, Council of, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Agronomy, Dept. of, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Agronomy, Dept. of, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Agway, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Albersheim Project, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Alumni Affairs & Development, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Alumni Affairs & Development, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Alumni Affairs & Development, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Alumni Affairs & Development, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- American Indian Program, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- American Indian Program, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- American Institute of Cooperation, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- American Institute of Cooperation, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- American Institute of Cooperation, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- American Institute of Cooperation, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- American Institute of Cooperation, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- American Institute of Cooperation, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Animal Science, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Animal Science, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 39)
- Animal Science, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 40)
- Arnot Forest, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Arts & Sciences, College of, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Athletics, 1981-1983 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- B (General Correspondence), 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Bailey Hortorium, 1972-1983 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Bailey Hortorium, 1972-1983 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Baker, E.V. Farm (Donor), 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Baker, E.V. Farm (Donor), 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Baker, E.V. Farm (Donor), 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Biochemistry, Molecular & Cell Biology, Section of, 1978-1983 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Biological Sciences, Division of, 1978-1983 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Biological Sciences, Division of, 1978-1983 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Biology Teachers--Leadership Development Program, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Biometrics, 1981-1983 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Biotechnology, Center for--Application for Designation, Volume 1, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Biotechnology, Center for--Application for Designation, Volume 1, cont., 1982 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Biotechnology, Center for--Application for Designation, Volume 2, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Biotechnology, Center for--Application for Designation, Volume 3, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Biotechnology, Center for--Application for Designation, Volume 4, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Biotechnology, Center for--Application for Designation, Volume 4, cont., 1982 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Biotechnology, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Biotechnology, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Biotechnology, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Biotechnology, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Biotechnology, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Biotechnology, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Biotechnology Institute, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Botany, 1978-1983 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, 1980-1983 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, 1980-1983 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, 1980-1983 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, 1980-1983 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, 1980-1983 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, 1980-1983 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Business & Public Administration, Graduate School, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- C (General Correspondence), 1981-1983 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Campus Affairs, Vice President for (William D. Gurowitz), 1981-1983 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- CARET (Committee for Agricultural Research, Extension and Teaching), 1982 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- CARET (Committee for Agricultural Research, Extension and Teaching), 1982 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- China, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- China--Nanjing, 1981-1983 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- China--Nanjing, 1981-1983 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- CISER (Cornell Institute for Social & Economic Research), 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- CISER (Cornell Institute for Social & Economic Research), 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Cohn Foundation, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Colenco (Columbia Environmental Corp.), 1979-1984 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Communication Arts, Dept. of, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Communication Arts, Dept. of, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Computers, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Cooperative Extension, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Cooperative Extension, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Cooperative Extension, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Cooperative Extension--New York City, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- County Agents--Photo enclosed, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Counsel (University), 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Counsel (University), 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Cornell Lab for Environmental Applications of Remote Sensing (CLEARS), 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Cornell Plantations, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Cornell Plantations, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Cornell Plantations, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Cornell Plantations, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Cuba Cheese, 1976-1983 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- CURW (Cornell United Religious Work), 1981-1989 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- D (General Correspondence), 1981-1983 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Dairy, 1981-1984 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Dairylea, 1982-1992 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Dairy Marketing Council, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- Dairy Records Processing Lab, 1982-1984 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Dairy Records Processing Lab, 1982-1984 (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Dean's Council, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Dean's Council, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Dean's Statutory Meeting, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 36)
- Dean's Statutory Meeting, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 37)
- Dean of Students, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Dickey, John Corporation, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 39)
- E (General Correspondence), 1982-1984 (Box 15, Folder 40)
- Ecology & Systematics, 1978-1983 (Box 15, Folder 41)
- Education, NYS Dept. of, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 42)
- Education, NYS Dept. of, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 43)
- Education, NYS Dept. of, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 44)
- Engineering, College of, 1982-1984 (Box 15, Folder 45)
- Egner, John--Associate Provost, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Entomology, Dept. of, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Entomology, Dept. of, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Entomology--Geneva--Chairman, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Environmental Research, Center for, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Equalization & Assessment, Division of, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Equalization & Assessment, Division of, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Equalization & Assessment, Division of, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Equalization & Assessment, Division of, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Equalization & Assessment, Division of, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- F (General Correspondence), 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Facilities Planning & Construction (Paul Griffen, Vice President), 1982 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Faculty--CALS, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Faculty--Committee on Economic Status of Statutory, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Faculty Honors, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Faculty Luncheon for New Faculty, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Faculty Meetings--CALS, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Faulty Reception for New Faculty, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Faculty--University, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Farm Credit Banks, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 20)